<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SkyCast</string>

    <!-- Home Fragment Text -->
    <string name="welcomeSign">Welcome to SkyCast</string>
    <string name="weatherButton">LOAD</string>

    <!-- Help Fragment Text -->
    <string name="helpIntro">Welcome to SkyCast! This guide will cover key features of the app and
    navigation directions. Scroll to a specific section for details. Happy Scrolling!</string>
    <string name="helpSectionHeader_Main"> How to Use SkyCast </string>
    <string name="helpSectionText_Main1"> In the Home screen, you\'ll find a dropdown menu to select
        your preferred city. Press the \"LOAD\"</string>
    <string name="helpSectionText_Main2">
        button to obtain the latest weather information for
        that city. The app will fetch and display the current weather information for that city by
        displaying the weather icon and temperature using live data from our API.</string>
    <string name="citySectionHeader_Main"> Manage Your Favorite Locations </string>
    <string name="helpSectionText_City1">The City Fragment allows you to customize your weather
        experience by selecting the cities you care</string>
    <string name="helpSectionText_City2">
        about most. Simply check the boxes next to your
        preferred cities, and they\’ll be instantly added to the dropdown menu in the Home Fragment.
        This makes it easy to quickly switch between locations and stay updated on the weather
        wherever you go. Want to de-clutter your list? Just uncheck a city, and it will be removed
        from the Home Fragment dropdown. Tailor your weather app to your needs in just a few
        taps!</string>
    <string name="helpSectionHeader_Profile"> Want to Meet the Team? </string>
    <string name="helpSectionText_Profile1">  Get to know the minds behind the Weather App! The
        Profile Fragment introduces you to our team of</string>
    <string name="helpSectionText_Profile2"> passionate developers, designers, and
        innovators. Learn more about the team committed to delivering accurate and reliable weather
        updates by visiting our profile page. </string>


    <string-array name="static_city_list">
        <item>Select a city</item>
        <item>Boston</item>
        <item>New York</item>
        <item>Los Angeles</item>
        <item>Chicago</item>
        <item>San Francisco</item>
        <item>Houston</item>
        <item>Seattle</item>
        <item>Miami</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="addCities">+</string>

    ` <!-- Profile Fragment-->
    <string name="theo_description1">
        Theodor Farag a Computer Science student passionate about building innovative and user-centric applications. Currently, I am contributing to a weather app project that delivers real-time weather updates and forecasts. My role involves
        integrating APIs to fetch and display dynamic weather data, developing
    </string>
    <string name="theo_description2">
         user-friendly interface components, and collaborating in an agile development environment to ensure efficient and iterative progress.
        This project has allowed me to strengthen my skills in back-end and front-end development while focusing on creating an intuitive and seamless user experience.
    </string>
    <string name="theodor_farag">Theodor Farag</string>`
    `    <string name="angelos_boules">Angelos Boules</string>
    <string name="angelos_description1">
        Angelos Boules is a talented Computer Science student with a passion for back-end development and problem-solving. As a key contributor to the weather app project, Angelos is responsible for developing the back-end infrastructure and implementing all the core logic that powers the app\’s
    </string>

    <string name="angelos_description2">
        functionality. He also assists with designing and refining the user interface and collaborates across all components of the project to ensure a seamless and efficient user experience. His dedication to building robust systems and his attention to detail have been instrumental in driving the app\’s success.
    </string>
    <string name="afsa_nafe">Afsa Nafe</string>
    <string name="afsa_description1">
        Afsa Nafe is a dedicated Computer Science student with a passion for user interface design and front-end development. As the lead for the UI of the weather app project, Afsa is responsible for creating an intuitive, visually appealing, and user-friendly interface. They focus on ensuring that the app
    </string>
    <string name="afsa_description2">
                provides a seamless experience for users by optimizing layout, responsiveness, and accessibility. Afsa’s creativity and attention to detail play a vital role in bringing the app’s features to life and enhancing the overall user experience.
    </string>`


</resources>