<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SkyCast</string>

    <!-- Home Fragment Text -->
    <string name="welcomeSign">Welcome to SkyCast</string>
    <string name="weatherButton">LOAD</string>

    <!-- Help Fragment Text -->
    <string name="helpIntro">Welcome to SkyCast! This guide will cover key features of the app and
    navigation directions. Scroll to a specific section for details. Happy Scrolling!</string>
    <string name="helpSectionHeader_Main"> How to Use SkyCast </string>

    <string name="helpSectionText_Main1"> In the Home screen, you\'ll find a dropdown menu to select
        your preferred city. Press the \"LOAD\"</string>
    <string name="helpSectionText_Main2">
        button to obtain the latest weather information for
        that city. The app will fetch and display the current weather information for that city by
        displaying the weather icon and temperature using live data from our API.</string>

    <string name="helpSectionText_Main_Landscape">
        In the Home screen, you\'ll find a dropdown menu to select
        your preferred city. Press the \"LOAD\" button to obtain the latest weather information for
        that city. The app will fetch and display the current weather information for that city by
        displaying the weather icon and temperature using live data from our API.
    </string>

    <string name="citySectionHeader_Main"> Manage Your Favorite Locations </string>

    <string name="helpSectionText_City1">The City Fragment allows you to customize your weather
        experience by selecting the cities you care</string>
    <string name="helpSectionText_City2">
        about most. Simply check the boxes next to your
        preferred cities, and they\’ll be instantly added to the dropdown menu in the Home Fragment.
        This makes it easy to quickly switch between locations and stay updated on the weather
        wherever you go. Want to de-clutter your list? Just uncheck a city, and it will be removed
        from the Home Fragment dropdown. Tailor your weather app to your needs in just a few
        taps!</string>

    <string name="helpSectionText_City_Landscape">The City Fragment allows you to customize your weather
        experience by selecting the cities you care about most. Simply check the boxes next to your
        preferred cities, and they\’ll be instantly added to the dropdown menu in the Home Fragment.
        This makes it easy to quickly switch between locations and
        </string>
    <string name="helpSectionText_City_Landscape2">stay updated on the weather
        wherever you go. Want to de-clutter your list? Just uncheck a city, and it will be removed
        from the Home Fragment dropdown. Tailor your weather app to your needs in just a few
        taps!</string>

    <string name="helpSectionHeader_Profile"> Want to Meet the Team? </string>

    <string name="helpSectionText_Profile1">  Get to know the minds behind the Weather App! The
        Profile Fragment introduces you to our team of</string>
    <string name="helpSectionText_Profile2"> passionate developers, designers, and
        innovators. Learn more about the team committed to delivering accurate and reliable weather
        updates by visiting our profile page. </string>

    <string name="helpSectionText_Profile_Landscape"> Get to know the minds behind the Weather App! The
        Profile Fragment introduces you to our team of passionate developers, designers, and
        innovators. Learn more about the team committed to delivering accurate and reliable weather
        updates by visiting our profile page. </string>

    <string-array name="static_city_list">
        <item>Select a city</item>
        <item>Boston</item>
        <item>New York</item>
        <item>Los Angeles</item>
        <item>Chicago</item>
        <item>San Francisco</item>
        <item>Houston</item>
        <item>Seattle</item>
        <item>Miami</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="addCities">+</string>

    <!-- Profile Fragment-->
    <string name="missionStatement">Our mission is to create a simple, uncluttered weather app that delivers essential
        information at a glance.
    </string>
    <string name="profileHeader"> Meet the Team!</string>
    <string name="theo_description1">
        Theodor Farag a Computer Science student passionate about building innovative and
        user-centric applications. His role in SkyCast involves
    </string>

    <string name="theo_description2">
        integrating an API to fetch and display weather data and develop user-friendly interface.
    </string>

    <string name="theo_desc_landscape">
        Theodor Farag a Computer Science student passionate about building innovative and
        user-centric applications. His role in SkyCast involves integrating an API to fetch and
        display weather data and develop user-friendly interface.
    </string>

    <string name="theodor_farag">Theodor Farag</string>
    <string name="angelos_boules">Angelos Boules</string>
    <string name="angelos_description1">
        Angelos Boules is a Computer Science student with a passion for back-end development and
        problem-solving. He is
    </string>

    <string name="angelos_description2">
         responsible for developing the back-end core logic and functionality. He also assists with
        designing the user interface.
    </string>

    <string name="angelos_desc_landscape">
        Angelos Boules is a Computer Science student with a passion for back-end development
        and problem-solving. He is responsible for developing the back-end core logic and
        functionality. He also assists with designing the user interface.
    </string>

    <string name="afsa_nafe">Afsa Nafe</string>

    <string name="afsa_description1">
        Afsa Nafe is a dedicated Computer Science student with a passion for user interface design
        and front-end development.
    </string>

    <string name="afsa_description2">
        As the lead for the UI of SkyCast, he is responsible for creating a visually appealing, and
        user-friendly interface. His animations and design bring the
        app’s features to life.
    </string>

    <string name = "afsa_desc_landscape">
        Afsa Nafe is a dedicated Computer Science student with a passion for user interface design
        and front-end development. As the lead for the UI of SkyCast, he is responsible for creating
        a visually appealing, and user-friendly interface. His animations and design bring the
        app’s features to life.
    </string>

    <string name="feels_like">Feels Like</string>


</resources>